SANKET KASTURE

Technical Skills

Python, Numpy, Pandas, Django Flask, postgresql, Mysql, Linux, Java, Microsoft excel, Office.

Contact

Address:

Mira Road Thane

Phone:

9967185105

Email:

sanketkasture1@gmail.com

Certifications

- -SIX SIGMA YELLOW BELT 2016
- -Basic PYTHON 2020 UDEMY.
- -Python essentials Coursera
- -Python programming NIELT

Languages

English Marathi Hindi

DOB

15/06/1990

Summary

Dependable and self-motivated professional with 3+ years experience in BFSI sector. Seeking to start a career in Tech industry with Strong background in Software development ,Finance, project management and customer relations.

Skill Highlights

- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- Negotiation Skills
- Innovative
- Service-focused

Experience

• Madhya Pradesh Gramin bank Pansemal, MP

Manager (August 2019 - January 2020)

- -The day to day banking activities like to handle Books of banks, help customer make the public relationship, manage cash book
- Maintaining credit profile like distribution of loan, decrease NPA of Bank, Loan recovery, Maintain books of loan takers.
- Implementation of government schemes like PMJDY, PMJJY, CM awas yojana, ATAL Pension yojana, PM rojgar yojana.
- Financial Inclusion like to help people in Rural areas to access financial products which are beneficial to them by conducting Periodic financial literacy camp and seminars.

LIC of India Mumbai

Development Officer (June 2016- May 2018)

- -Employ agents for selling or marketing LIC policies -Providing training to recruited agents
- -Analyzing overall performance of each agent
- -Finding out agents capabilities and shortcomings
- -Motivating agents to procure maximum sales in a given time -A ssign target quota to agents
- -Maintaining overall integrity in sales

Clarion Mediaz Thane

Software Developer (Java) August 2014 – March 2015

• ITsource Technologies, Mumbai

Software Developer (Java) Feb 2014- July 2014

- -Requirement analysis and gathering
- -Software Development Life Cycle

Education

MET Institute of Management Mumbai

MMS (Finance) 2017

 Bharati Vidyapeeth College Of Engineering Navi Mumbai

BE(IT) 2013